Kristopher Kohlmeier

Media Technologies

kristopherkohlmeier@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/kris-kohlmeier/ +1 (805)-276-4713

Early career software engineer with an emphasis towards media technologies. Fast learner with a proven record of quick thinking and solution execution in live production environments. Experience with agile development patterns and delivering software in team environments.

Work Experience

Production Technology Assistant

Jun 2021 - Present

Crossroads Church | Camarillo

Operated part-time as the main point person in charge of A/V production equipment on a weekly basis. Supported volunteer teams as well as staff members with A/V related tasks and training.

- Planned and executed over \$40,000 in A/V installs and upgrade projects.
- Onboarded new stage lighting console for production volunteers, offering training, on-call support, and programming when needed.
- Utilized projection mapping to bring a unique look to the stage for holiday special events.
- Personally repaired out of warranty stage lights to preserve production budget.

Animation Technology Internship

Jun 2023 - Aug 2023

Skydance Animation Studios | Santa Monica

Three month long internship to work with and learn from five different technology departments in an animation studio.

- Audited studio codebase, leveraging Rez API with a python script for the pipeline engineers.
- Created SOP for and assisted in the integration of a studio-wide printer system.
- Created a tracking document for all editorial hardware during studio location moves.
- · Solved Jira Tickets for the general IT help desk.

Projects

Story Development Software

Jan 2024 - May 2024

Prototype server and client that ingested storyboard panels and .EDL files to track editorial changes for a film in early production. Created as a senior project and developed with mySQL and Python.

Padoq Nov 2024 - Present

Web application being developed with a small team as a joint venture to eventually bring to market. Current technology stack includes Vue, Ionic, and Firebase.

Core Skills

HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Vue, Python, C, SQL, Docker, Lighting Design, A/V drawing and installation

Education

California State University

Jan 2021 - Jun 2024

Bachelor of Science Computer Science GPA 3.4